One dream.
One wish.
If you want it, gotta go over the top.
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marks maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top!
Kawamatsu!
My dear friend!
I'd lost hope!
Yet here you are before me!
Indeed.
And all it took was 13 years of
poisonous fish, day after day.
Let me see your face, Kawamatsu.
Alas, I am bound by chains.
When will the battle occur?
Nine days from now, on the
night of the fire festival.
Ah, what delicious irony, taking Kaido's
head in the celebration meant to honor him.
I'm sorry to ask this, but could
you please free me from here?
Of course I will.
I'll see to it post-haste, though
I'm faced with several obstacles.
I'll need the keys to
your cell and your chains.
Let us hope they aren't
too rusted to open.
Hold on.
There's someone in front
of the forbidden cell.
His head is massive.
That's got to be the key thief.
We found the guy.
Commander Solitaire, what should we do?
Un-key!
Capture him, you fools!
Uh-oh.
Smoke escaped Jutsu!
He disappeared!
Must be a ninja! Find him!
Oh, right.
I think we have enough guards going
after the key thief right now.
Let's party!
Good.
Now escort these gentlemen
to their execution. Yes, sir!
Come on, this way.
Here we go, baby!
Yeah!
It's Master Queen's special device
performance, the Sumo Inferno!
Sumo?
What the hell?
This collar here is the same as
the ones you got around your necks.
Imagine this stone pillar is one of you.
Now let's see what happens if you try
to leave the ring with your collar on,
shall we?
Whoa, that's intense.
So before trying anything naughty,
you should know that these
collars are equipped with blades.
strong enough to cut through stone.
Or in this case, your
little necks. No fair!
It's like what the Celestial Dragons used!
I appreciate the spirit,
kid, but you really think you can
pull the thing off just like that?
Keep winning matches, and your head
gets to stay attached to your neck.
But step out of the
ring and you're a toast.
You two are a team, by the way,
so the execution isn't complete until
both of you fall out of the ring.
Also, if you change your
mind and decide to join us,
then Straw Hat and only
Straw Hat will be released.
As for your opponents, they'll have
weapons, no collars, and limitless numbers.
I'll keep them coming
for as long as I choose.
So I'll do you one favor,
just to make things more fair.
Let's uncuff you, boys, so
you don't die in round one.
Huh? What?
After all the trouble I went through?
Was this the wrong key?
So the mission was a
bust from the very start?
Thank you!
I thought you were a bad guy,
but you're actually pretty nice.
With those dumb cuffs off,
I'm practically free already.
What?
But I just put something
even worse on you.
Did you forget you're wearing a
collar that can chop your head off?
What?
Oh, that's right.
Wait a minute.
If the two of us have to fight as
a team, then I'll only hold Mr.
Straw Hat back.
Can't you execute us separately?
Hey, Balloon!
Oh, Balloon!
Please don't provoke him.
If I kick your round ass hard enough,
will you let us out of this place?
There you are.
So you're the bastard
who stole my sword, huh?
I'll be taking it back now.
You are the one who
stole that sacred blade.
I have reclaimed Shusui and returned
it to the only place that it belongs.
That flamed sword is a
national treasure that
was taken from the grave of
the legendary samurai, Ryuma.
Yeah, I know.
Then shut your mouth and leave this place.
If you do not, I will gladly steal
the two swords at your waist as well.
I warn you.
You a weapon collector or what?
That's quite a haul.
What are you going to do with them?
As it turns out, my friends could put
those weapons to good use right now.
Lucky timing, you might say.
Since you think stealing is fair game.
I'll take everything you've got!
You should have fled while you
had the chance, mountain bandit!
Sorry, but there seems
to be a misunderstanding.
To be clear, I'm a pirate.
Oh, I'm going to enjoy crushing you.
He'll learn soon.
A couple of rounds and
he'll beg for mercy.
The rules are completely stacked against
him, and he's too stupid to see it.
He thinks this is a tournament
when it's an execution.
All right, men, start lining up.
You all get your shot.
Show them hell!
Deathmatch, go!
No, there's too many of them.
Not only do we outnumber you,
we're all armed to the teeth.
We don't have to follow any rules.
Is it starting to sink in?
It's only a matter of time before
both of you are chopped to bits.
Yes, let's go!
Rest in peace, old man, yo.
Rest in peace, Mr. Straw Hat.
Positions ready!
Get ready!
Go!
You prisoners are lucky to get
a front row seat to the murder
show better behave or it'll be
you up here next Ha ha ha ha!
Keep them coming!
Those guys weren't even
a good enough warm-up!
Are you kidding me?
He didn't even touch them!
Oh.
So he can use the Conqueror's Haki.
Who are you?
All right, it's time to up the ante.
Pleasures!
It's your time to shine!
It's been an uproar every
day since you showed up.
But if you can protect Yoguro,
that's all that matters.
I'm counting on you, Lufitaro.
It's a raid.
That's Hawkins.
He's a headliner from the Beast Pirates.
No one moves an inch.
This is a bathhouse.
What could you want from us?
A bathhouse is perfect for
our job today If everyone's
naked that means they can't
hide anything from us.
Hey, Drake, get in here.
What are you doing?
There's nothing of interest
to me in the bathhouse.
My job is to take down Sabo Mask.
You can do the rest of the
dirty work on your own.
What are we gonna do, Shinobu?
If they sent in someone like Hawkins,
then they must be here for us.
How did they know where to find us?
Those cheaters, literally
catching us with our pants down.
Shall we fight?
We'll keep that as a last resort.
A mature woman doesn't use
her weapons carelessly.
Hide behind me, ladies, quickly.
Now, I want everyone here to line up.
Show us your ankles.
If any of you have a reversed
crescent moon tattoo,
then I'm afraid you'll
need to come with me.
Everyone soaking in the bath
must step out immediately.
They know about that?
How is that even possible?
Check them all. Yes!
Did the plan get leaked?
Who is that hiding behind you?
Show yourself!
Don't worry, I'll back you
up if something happens.
Oh, sorry, did you mean
me? I wasn't hiding.
I'm just a normal customer
taking a hot bath.
So it's you.
She's dynamite!
Her body's a national treasure!
A deadly art.
Come on, seriously?
A happy punch straight to my heart!
Bandits, a knockout!
What?
Wait, that's the guy from yesterday.
Soap mask!
Nami.
The shape of your body was like a
magnificent river flowing through heaven.
Sanchi, what is he doing here?
And what is he wearing, that idiot?
Hey, Drake, is silver mask inside?
He was there all along.
Hey, bring me silver mask!
Huh?
I said...
If you're that weak to naked women, then
you should have informed me beforehand.
Who you calling weak?
Drake, you're originally from
the North Blue, aren't you?
Yeah, same as you. What of it?
Then look, that man should seem familiar.
Ugh!
Stealth black from Germa double six!
But Al, why?
Don't you dare run from us!
The search isn't over yet!
Come on, let's go!
You filler!
You think I'm afraid of you?
Look out, Sabo Mask!
It seems he has
teleportation tech as well.
Hang on tight, ladies.
He's flying! Follow him!
Only Stealth Black could
have pulled that off.
I'll get him next time.
You wanna explain yourself?
It's a long story.
I'll tell you once we're safe.
You're bleeding. Profusely.
If I die now, I die happy. I'll be fine.
That's the least of our concerns now that
they've found out about the ankle tattoos.
Indeed.
It seems we have a traitor
in our midst. Yeah.
And I'm afraid that's not all.
I heard some more bad news
before I went to the bathhouse.
Beppo, Penguin, and
Chouchou were taken captive.
The Beast Pirates must
be aiming for Traffy.
They nabbed his friends to
use his bait to lure him out.
In that case, it's likely
their plan will work.
He may be a grump, but
he cares about his crew.
We'll try to stop him for now.
We can't afford to throw
the capital into chaos.
You still haven't told us why
you were at the bathhouse.
How much longer till I get my yummy treat?
I'm gonna pass out soon if I don't eat.
Are we there yet?
Tell me, Chuck Raymond, I
would love a little snack.
You're giving me that look again!
It shouldn't be too much longer, Olene!
Hang in there!
First, we say big bow!
After that...
It's time to Shit!
I'm something big!
Yes!
Will you also enjoy a bowl with me, Otama?
Huh?
Yes, ma 'am.
It's the best.
Otsuru gave me some on my birthday.
I'll never forget it.
It's like it was dancing inside my mouth.
It's a happiness spread all the way
from my head down to my tippy toes.
I thought my ginger bubble exploded.
It was so yummy.
Yep, that's right.
Red beans are such a delight.
Red bean paste, don't let
it go to waste. Ah-ha.
Rice cake.
Best friends with red beans!
Together they make the
most deliciousest treat!
I bet that you can't name a Tsuru bear!
Agreed!
And the way the little pieces of mochi
shine like a frog's eye, it's collectible!
Sorry, like a what?
Wait a sec.
You don't eat eyeballs, do you, Olene?
No!
I was just pointing out the similarity.
Though almost anything
looks good, my dear.
I'm not edible! Stop! Mama!
If I can't get it, I'll go mad.
You're rather excited over this meal.
Your certainness is okay?
They don't know anymore. Huh?
I must stop!
What's gonna happen when she
finds out there is no Oshiruko?
Is the devastating truth gonna
shock her back into being big mom?
STRIKE!
This is going to make the rescue
mission even more dangerous!
What should I do?
What can I do?
Oh, man!
Another survey!
Right away!
Luffy Toto wins!
He did it!
That's amazing.
You took down all the pleasures with ease.
Almost.
What do you mean, almost?
You wiped the floor with those guys.
I don't get how Rayleigh does it.
I think, like this, maybe?
Rayleigh? Yeah.
Luffy, it's called armament Haki.
Think of it as covering
yourself in invisible armor.
I watched Rayleigh send an elephant
flying without even touching it.
That's the first time he showed me Haki.
It must have been insanely strong.
I need to learn how to use that.
This is taking too long!
Just let me get in there already, I'll
kill that little punk in ten seconds flat!
What would be the fun in that, huh?
Sumo Inferno's at its best
when it's dragged out. Huh?
Look, I'll break it down for you.
The more people involved,
the longer the fight.
The longer the fight,
the more the suffering.
This whole production
is about crushing his
spirit slowly but surely until he croaks.
Get out of here with that efficiency crap!
This is about entertainment.
Which you clearly don't
know the first thing about?
Why don't you go and fetch me more?
Another?
Damn, haven't you had enough?
Slow it down Go to hell!
It's more than just food.
It's like air to me.
For you, sir.
Uh-huh!
Ah, what impeccable time
is exactly what I wanted.
This is my all-time favorite.
How'd you know?
It's Supreee-me.
Send him flying with my invisible armor.
I'll figure it out somehow.
Mr.
Straw Hat, what are you talking about?
All right.
Let's practice.
Give me your worst.
I actually met with Yuma, you know.
How dare you lie!
What do you claim is impossible?
Did you think I would fall
for such an obvious ruse?
I mean, I saw his body, the
soul was someone else's.
Sounds like you've lost your mind to me!
You know nothing of Ryuma!
He was a legendary swordsman,
able to take down any opponents
in the blink of an eye!
You're an ingrate, incapable of
understanding the greatness of Shusui!
That blade is a treasure to the
people here, IT BELONGS TO REYUMON!
Many years ago, the world once
referred to our beloved country.
as the Land of Gold. Oh yeah?
Then why is that?
You're open!
Pirates across the world lusted
after the wealth of our land.
And the world nobles too.
They longed to rule over us.
However, there was only one man who stood
up to the avaricious enemies from abroad.
He burned the name of our samurai
into the pages of history.
That man was our hero, Ryuma.
Many legends surround his name.
However, one in particular
is the most famous.
It's a tale of him slaying a dragon
that once flew over the capital.
Upon his death, he was laid to rest
with his trusted weapon, Chouchou.
He was consecrated as God of the Blade!
Ryuma and Chouchou belong
to the people of Wano!
Fine, then.
You made your point.
But you know, none of that's
got anything to do with me.
It's time for me to take back Shusui.
I feel off my game
swinging around two swords.
It seems as if I have overestimated you.
Shusui is a black blade It is Ryumas You
are not the one who forged it in battle
You're not a swordsman like he was You're
just a hoodlum With no
integrity to speak of
Forged?
I was wondering about that
Someone help!
Huh?
You're open!
You asshole!
Don't stab me in the back when
someone is crying for help!
You thought I wouldn't take
advantage of an opening?
This is a fight to the death I will win!
Please save us!
Our lives are in danger! Look!
It's a samurai!
Hey!
Can you help us?
Are they serious?
The laughing is throwing me off.
Mr.
Swordsman, sir!
I beg of you!
Please help us!
Blood.
Guess they're serious after all.
One second, wait!
You're open!
I told you to wait!
Damn it!
Can't you take a hint, man?
We are still in a duel!
I am not finished with you yet! I know!
We'll fight, but give me a minute!
You think everyone forgot about
the murder you committed, Zorojuro?
Here's a question, what
compels you to help them?
What about you?
Why do you have a beef with them?
I'm here for one thing,
to cut down that little brat who
laughed at the shogun and ran away!
It's all right, Dock. I'm here.
I know who you are.
Yojito Kirikamazo, the serial
killer from the capital.
But it's clear you're actually an
assassin that works for Orochi.
Who else would have reason to come after
a harmless young girl's life like this?
The nerve of you addressing the
Shogun without his proper title.
You're an interesting one.
Who are you?
You're a samurai, aren't you?
Please help us.
Well, lucky for you,
I'm not exactly the type of man to watch a
woman and a kid get
slaughtered before my eyes.
I'll do anything to pay you back.
We'll call it even for a meal and sake.
Deal.
Well, I'm in.
Fine by me, I was already granted permission
to dismantle anyone who gets in my way.
I'm sure I'm gonna catch hell from your
boss, but I'm kicking your ass either way.
Not to worry—you'll be dead before
you can even catch your breath!
breath
He's pretty tough.
It's about time you got serious.
You're lucky I don't have my sword.
This would be easy.
I'm unbearably hungry.
Do you think that maybe,
if I'm all a meal good,
I could get dibs on a
stash of prison dumplings?
That's fine.
Show him who's boss.
That's what I like to hear.
Thanks for the positivity.
I'm going to get him. You what?
Now prepare yourself!
Nice try.
But that barely hurts.
Please, Mr.
Straw Hat, just wait.
I know he looks quite
cuddly on the exterior.
But keep in mind the bear's
claws are powerful enough?
to tear through human
flesh like it's paper.
Be on your guard.
I'll send you fly!
No contact!
Sucks!
Keep accidentally hitting them!
Wait, what do you mean?
Isn't hitting them the whole point?
What are you trying to do?
It's fine.
Send in more!
Come on!
Ah!
Shit!
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Oh, Brad!
I can't pull it out!
Hope you don't mind if
I borrow this for a sec.
What is he doing?
He's trying to use three weapons?
Three-sword style!
Purgatory!
Onigiri!
Ah!
What strength! Stunning!
And here he comes.
I really have to do this now?
Mr. Samurai!
Thank you.